The Clover Kingdom.
In this place where magic is everything,
there lives one boy who was born without it.
His name is Asta.
His strength and determination helped him become a magic knight.
And despite the many challenges he faces,
he aims for the top and refuses to give up.
Rich or poor, royalty or commoner,
Asta believes anyone can shine.
His mission is to prove that to the whole world
and to become the next Wizard King.
In order to defeat Megicula,
the devil lurking in the Spade King,
the magic knights have been training hard.
In the briny depths of the sea,
another dangerous threat has emerged.
Kyoto, Kohono, you two make a run for it!
We can't!
You must!
Seek the aid of the magic knights!
Come on, we've gotten this far!
Dad!
Father!
He's right. Let's go.
Okay.
I'll see you next time.
Bye!
I'm right back up to the sea.
Let's go, bye!
Bye!
Yeah, yeah, yeah
強く風吹く世界の果てで
僕らは今日も目を閉じる夢を見る飽きもせず
今は小さく儚い希望も
いつか時代を変えてゆく光になると信じて
背負うべきものなど何一つないさ
全て抱きしめてゆく
例えばそれが痛みだとしても
叶うなら君と共に
この声がこの喉が振り切れるほど今叫ぶよ
未来は自分で切り開くんだって
とめどなく溢れてる情熱のままさ
歩き出そう
Fulfill my dream
The beach town of Rockway is hot year-round
due to the strong mana that surrounds it
This makes it a popular resort
but it is also an excellent training ground for magic users
Wlaughter Mages most of all
If I can just maintain this force
I can create two twisters now
But I need to keep them both supplied with mana
Is that crying?
A song?
I'm not sure why
But it feels sort of nostalgic
Wait, why did I just see my mother?
Black balls fight!
You feel that burn?
Oh yeah!
We pushed through it!
Are you out of steam already?
Well it's not like I run very often
I mean come on
What gives?
Why can't we just train with magic?
Because when we were fighting against the elves
Yami and Asta prove that this kind of training matters too
The stronger your body gets
The stronger your magic's gonna be
Right!
Come on!
Let's get to it, Finral!
Bulk up to you're as big as Captain Yami
And you'll be unstoppable!
Aren't you setting the bar kinda high?
We should all get super buff
And then all of you should try to fight me at the same time!
Round two, guys!
I want to hear that fighting spirit
Even louder this time!
AHHHHH!
Damn it!
I missed one
What the hell did you trap us for, you sneaky bastard?!
Last time I checked, the best way to train up your magic was to use it
So, that's just what I've been doing
I'd say sorry, but
I didn't join this squad to make friends with you idiots
What was that?!
Damn it, Luck!
Are you trying to bury us?!
You bet I am!
Here!
AHHHHH!
AHHHH!
AHH!
I can't hide my face while I'm doing this pose, it's so embarrassing!
I've been eating a whole lot of Charmy's cooking lately, and it's starting to show!
Gotta lose weight, gotta lose weight, gotta lose weight, gotta lose weight, gotta lose weight!
The simplest way to bulk up is to stress your muscles in a controlled manner.
When weight training, you should probably break up your workout into three sets.
You should also track your protein intake.
This info on the connection between the deltoids and trapezius proves that by gaining more anatomical knowledge, I can make my new Marie doll far more accurate.
Question for you, Gordon. I thought you said you had trouble spending time in the sun without getting burnt. Were you able to get over that?
Yes, I can stay out as long as I'd like to now. It's all thanks to this special sunblock. Would you care to try it out for yourself?
I'd love to. Thanks for offering.
You need to be meticulous when dealing with UV rays. Here you go.
That's cold. Just what do you think you're doing back there?
Huh? What?
Hello. Here you go.
Who the hell says you can't have beer for breakfast?
Captain, for you.
Thanks. Aren't you going to train like the rest of the squad?
Glad we talked.
Hey, guys! Food's ready! Come and get it!
Thanks for the meal!
It's that song again!
Eh? Noel?
This is about where I was the first time I heard it.
Hey!
Asta?
Did something happen or what?
Not exactly. But do you hear anything strange?
Like what?
Hey, look!
Wait, Kahono?
And Kieto!
What are you doing here?
I could ask the same, but since you're exactly who we're looking for, I'll chalk it up to Providence.
The sea goddess is as beautiful as ever.
So what gives? Is there trouble at home?
Oh, right. We came to ask for help.
It's bad. We ask that you meet us back at the temple.
You were attacked by a monster?
A strong one? Likely a guardian of the sea.
They've been around since time immemorial. They're said to be servants of the sea god.
So this creature is sacred? If you served the same god, then why would it attack you?
Something's begun to disturb the flow of mana in this part of the sea.
As a result, much of the local fauna has become quite aggressive.
I decided to investigate with magic, and then I saw it.
The mana disturbance made it hard to make out details.
But I know what I saw. South of this temple in a place called the Void of No Return, there lurks a guardian of the sea that has been wholly consumed by its own rage.
I'm sure that the disturbance I felt in the mana here was caused by this guardian's fury.
The temple mages might have calmed the guardian by performing their song and dance, but they never got a chance to try.
Our best warriors were wounded trying to defend us.
Kahono.
Well, we brought you here to request that you grant Kiyoto and Kahono your protection.
Please use your considerable strength to escort them to the Void of No Return safely.
Sounds like a whole lot of not my problem. We're all really busy training right now.
You spent all day drinking in a beach chair!
Please, sir. I ask because I know how powerful the Black Bulls are.
You proved this in the Battle Royale we fought, and through your ability to reach the underwater temple safely, despite being land dwellers.
Though that was through the Sea Goddess's protection.
This may sound harsh, but have you got any proof that your song and dance can actually calm this guardian down?
Not exactly.
Protecting the kingdom isn't a hobby for us. It's a job.
We need to put our efforts where we know they'll count.
I'm not about to loan you my squad members when your resolve is this week.
So basically, we just need to convince you that this could work.
Huh? What do you mean?
This mana disturbance is affecting a massive part of the sea.
It's possible that there's a devil behind this, too.
As magic knights, we are sworn to protect.
I'll get your mages to the Guardian safely. There's no doubt in my mind.
Noelle.
The Sea Goddess provides.
I'm sure now, we'll quell the Guardian's rage. You have my word.
We've sung and danced for the Almighty Sea God. We're prepared for this task.
One way or another, we will make the Guardian hear our prayers.
That's the kind of resolve I can get behind.
Now, convince me it'll work.
I have a plan. And I think you'll like it.
It's over there. See it?
The Void of No Return.
Its name is based on the legend that those who wander into its depths are never seen again.
We were told stories as kids, but I never thought they were real.
Even now, it's a bit of a struggle to believe my eyes.
How deep do you think this goes?
So, what's your plan?
I'll make a smaller and more powerful version of the Sea Dragon's Cradle.
There's a trade-off. It'll be durable, but it won't carry more than four people.
Well, with you, Kahano, and Kyoto, we've already got our first three passengers.
Well, we could still fit one more...
Me! Me! Me!
Please, oh man, I want to go so bad!
Why sing to the Guardian when we could kill it?
I wonder how strong it is. I can't wait to find out!
Just send me and I'll get it done quickly.
Marie awaits me. Her deltoids need carving.
Please tell me there's something I'm missing here!
Maybe this Guardian wants to rejoin the cycle of life!
Talk about well-aged meat, am I right?
Yeah, I'm not sending any of you.
What?
And you're not going either.
Are you serious, sir? Why?
Is it because I can't swim?
Forgot about that. You really can't go.
This isn't fair!
He's such an idiot.
Fenril, you go.
Huh?
Get him out if things go bad.
Even if you have to die to do it.
Understood?
Yes, sir!
Oh, and Noel.
You're the one who decided to do this, so make sure you see it through.
Sir!
Such violent mana.
If I let my guard down for even a second, we're finished.
Look there!
What the heck are those?
I don't know.
We've never seen anything like them before.
Kahano!
Leave it to me, brother.
Now!
Song magic!
Mother lullaby!
It's strange, but my guess is that the local fish were turned into monsters by the powerful mana that's concentrated around the Guardian.
Is that even possible?
We're surrounded!
There's no end to these things.
We'll just have to push through them.
Noelle?
Just sit tight and leave this to us!
Song magic!
Destructive beat!
Wait!
Don't be stupid!
Hold on a second!
Together!
Right!
Combo spell!
Seek God's descent!
There's too many of them!
What do we do?
What's wrong with me?
I'm supposed to protect those two, not stand by and watch while they do all the fighting.
Get out of here, Noelle!
Carol, are you hearing yourself?
I can't leave while you're down here.
If I did, then you'd be thrown into the ocean!
It'll be fine.
Once I grab those two, I'll meet you back at the temple.
But how are you gonna pull that off?
Look, the captain said to bring everyone back.
He said to do it even if it kills me.
And I might be a screw-up, but I'm not so bad that I'd abandon a girl in a place like this.
Now, get out of here!
But you can't.
Noelle!
Kahano!
Mom.
Everyone.
I can't just give up.
That's right.
I can't let this be the end for me.
If I die here, then I'll never be able to take vengeance on the devil that killed my mother!
You see, spirit guardians are able to wield powerful magic by borrowing energy from natural mana.
But they cannot defeat a devil.
Natural mana.
This water's teeming with it.
I just need to get it on my side.
Please, lend me your strength!
No way.
I don't get it.
She'd need crazy magic control just to make more than one of these.
So how are they all so strong?
Well done.
You're even more amazing than I thought you were.
I'm sorry that it took me so long to think of this.
Now that we're safe, let's find that guardian!
Hey, what's that sound?
Damn, it's the Kraken!
Like the Guardian of the Sea, the Kraken is a fierce defender of the Sea God's domain.
So I'm guessing it wants us out of here.
Get in my mouth!
Nicely done, Finral.
Here it comes!
This ink, it's obstructing our vision
and disrupting the flow of mana
at this rate.
Water creation magic.
Valkyrie armor!
No Elf!
Sorry, but I need you to take a little nap!
This is our chance!
Right!
Looks like an ancient ruin.
Who would have thought?
I wonder who built all this?
Same.
Do you think people actually lived here?
It's the Guardian.
It has to be.
Such powerful mana.
It's like there's an aura of pure rage around it.
Is it threatening us?
I don't speak whale.
Oh!
Oh
I see the guardian hasn't turned bad. It's just protective of its baby
As for the creatures we fought, I suppose they must have been trying to help
Oh, I get it
So that's the sound I've been hearing. The lullaby you sing for your baby
Wait, that was my mother! Do you know her?
Oh
Sea goddess, thanks. I...
Hey, don't tell me you're injured
No, I'm fine. Just nostalgic
Strangely enough, it seems like mom might have come here before me
So I'm sure I was clumsier, and it must have taken far longer
I followed in her footsteps
See mom, I'm growing
Thank you so much for helping us
Are you really sure that this is all the thanks you need?
I think grandpa was hoping we'd get to throw a feast for you guys
This is gonna be delicious!
Wait, we could've had a feast?
You two take care, alright? And tell your grandpa hi
Come see us once things calm down
I've got a very special welcome in mind for the sea goddess
The four of us should do another double date
I'm sure it'll be a blast
Sure, I'll be looking forward to it
Hey, hold on a second
Kona's so forward, a girl after my own
No, stupid brain you have Lady Finnis, remember?
Good work down there
Ah, yummy
You know, it was in that temple you first started to turn from a good-for-nothing coward
To a man that fights with his squad
Yeah, I still remember that fight
But tell me this
Do you still remember what I said to you?
Before you got strong?
I figure that you've probably got your own way of fighting, don't you?
Yeah
I found my way of fighting
And now
I'm making strides towards my next goal
At least I'm trying
I'm trying
Good for you
There's just one more thing though
Sir?
You used your spatial magic to sick a giant squid leg on us, didn't you?
It was a spur of the moment thing, I'm sorry!
Yeah, I'm not in the mood for excuses
Oh, hey
Welcome back, guys
What's up, Henry?
It's good to see us
Well, anyway, I want some chow
Yeah, I'm starving
What are you making us charming?
We'll start off with a nice seafood barbecue
I want to show off the natural yumminess of the fish
A protein-rich meal
Wish I could send Marie some
I want to eat squid
Yeah, I'd be happy if I never saw a squid again
I'll keep getting stronger, Mom
Watch me
I'm just getting started
Noelle
Asta
You chase your goals and keep getting stronger
I'll chase mine until I become an idol
Next time on Black Clover, page 137
Charmy's Century of Hunger
Gordon's Millennium of Loneliness
Cheer for me, Kay!
Are you ready?
Will you get defeated?
I'll catch you
Because you're s !
Laadam
The other one looksץ
Aging